This intensity... It's just like Eris!
She's a Hyral Menas!
Get 'em!
Truly fortune favors me, that a Hyral Menas should be among my opponents!
Could there be any better way
to test the fruits of my training?
You're a Hyral Menas, right?
A Hyral Menas?
Rani, protect Seilyn and the others.
I'll handle her!
Y-Yeah...
You sure do look happy at times like these.
Oh, you can tell?
You're grinning from ear to ear.
A-Am I?
Anyway, keep them all safe, okay?
Got it!
I ask that you fight me instead.
Is this some kind of joke?
A weak girl like you
stands no chance against me.
Now, I'll just convert my aether to mana...
What?
Reborn
to Master the Blade
From Hero-King to Extraordinary Squire
Episode 4    The Town Ruled by the Highlander
Impossible...
Inglis's mana is this strong?
Burst! Shiny Flow!
Please don't hold back.
Very well.
I've been bored lately without
any good foes to fight.
She's so aggressive! I love it!
I'm liking her more and more by the second!
I think we'll get along.
I was just thinking the same thing.
Bratty little girl...
Draw your sword.
That won't be necessary.
What?
It's uselessly dull.
Time to find out if your words are true.
An ordinary knight would've been run through
before they could move a muscle.
Of course, if you couldn't dodge
this much, it'd be no fun at all!
She's maintaining her distance at all times,
even as she attacks with her spear!
Very good!
She keeps closing the distance
with each attack I make.
You're out of room to fall back.
Nice attack!
Mine wasn't half bad either.
Very good. She's strong enough to stand up
right after a hit like that.
And her desire to fight hasn't dulled at all!
Excellent!
You have so much power.
Why are you serving a Highlander?
Her kind are trying
to steal away the surface.
You're not just letting that happen.
You're actively helping them.
Well, Lady Seilyn seems nice.
And the people in town seemed to like her.
If you only look at what's
happening on the surface, sure.
Surface?
You didn't notice something
wrong about the town?
The flow of mana?
What about it?
If you noticed, then look into it yourself.
And realize for yourself
how foolish your deeds are.
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't a bit curious.
But unfortunately,
I'm not here to play hero!
I was just helping her to earn some money
after we ate too much and spent it all.
To earn money?
And thanks to that, I got to fight you!
So I'm grateful to all that food I ate.
What use is power without justice?
I get to have fun! That's all!
Fool!
I refuse to let somebody
like you have such power!
You did well to dodge that.
An attack that ignores space and distance...
So this is her true, hidden power.
Now this is getting interesting!
She keeps moving around...
I've been waiting for this!
So, what will you do now?
Fool! You've also stopped moving!
So she can kick, not just use her spear?
She knew what I'd do, too...
Now you're mine!
What?
That was a good fight, huh?
I had more fun than I thought I would.
How will I ever face them now?
Chris!
I dealt with the enemies outside!
Chris...
Rani!
I can't let myself be captured here.
Let me go, if you value her life.
Chris...
Go, then.
But may I say one thing?
You're free to do whatever
you want when fighting me.
Flee as many times as you like,
if you think things aren't going your way.
However, if you ever hurt Rani again...
You're a dead woman.
That's all.
Have a nice evening.
What's your name?
Inglis Eucus.
A pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Sistia Rouge.
Until we meet again...
Rani!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Sorry...
I guess I interrupted you.
No, I was done.
So were you, right?
Yes.
Lady Seilyn's safe.
Our mission's complete.
Yup.
Thank you so much for your help yesterday.
Thanks to you, none of my men were injured.
I'm glad we could help.
Are the former knights we captured
going to be executed?
No, they were once loyal
servants of this city.
They simply got a little arrogant.
I want them to change their ways and
use their strength not for themselves,
but for the weak and powerless.
I plan on taking my time
to persuade them of this.
And if they're willing to change,
I'm going to hire them again.
Wow! And to think they tried to kill you!
I think that's wonderful.
Oh? This has an unusual taste.
Yes. I thought you might be tired from
yesterday, so I've added some herbs to it.
I see.
I do feel relaxed,
like I could sleep very well.
Yes, it's good.
It is.
There's something I want
to talk to you about.
Will you come with me?
Y-Yes?
I didn't realize there was a place
like this under the castle.
Only a select few know of it.
That's...
This magic circle is draining away mana.
Lady Seilyn... What is this?
The core of the Highland.
A Levitation Circle.
It absorbs mana from its surroundings,
and when it has enough,
it breaks the land away from the earth
around it and brings it to the sky.
The sky?
Does that mean...?
It will become a new Highland.
Her kind are trying
to steal away the surface.
I thought she meant in the
political or psychological sense.
I didn't think she literally meant they
were stealing the surface itself...
If it flies up into the sky,
what happens to the people who live here?
The Highland is for Highlanders.
They'll either have to leave or become
slaves of Highlanders themselves.
I'm planning on asking the higher-ups
to let those who wish live here
without becoming slaves, or even allow them
to become Highlanders themselves.
Can you do that?
I will. Even if I have to fight the Highland.
Why are you telling us
something so important?
Because I wanted somebody
to forgive me, I guess.
My being here as this city's ruler
means it may someday be destroyed.
But I'm hiding that from everyone...
and I don't know if that's okay.
So I want to ask you...
Is it okay for me to be here?
If not, you may strike me down where I stand.
C-Chris, what do we say?
She's asking you for your opinion.
You need to tell her what you think.
What about you, Chris?
Me? I'll go with whatever you say.
I'm going to be your squire, after all.
That's not fair!
That's what it means to be the boss!
Okay...
Lady Seilyn...
I want to believe in you.
Because I think you believe what you say.
Rafinha...
When this land takes flight, if you
need my power, I'll come to help you.
I'm going to train at the knights' academy
in the capital and study hard!
I'll be able to help you more then!
So when that happens,
take me on as a knight here!
Thank you, Rafinha...
This is okay, right, Chris?
It's what I've decided for myself.
It's fine.
If things go well, we might get
to fight a Highlander army!
That's not going well at all!
What was that? An earthquake?
I heard voices from this direction!
Be careful, Rani!
A magicite beast!
That's...
No... Is that Lady Seilyn?
Why? There hasn't been any Prism Flow!
Rani, remember what
happened three years ago.
Three years ago?
Rahl was turned into a magicite beast
by the Bloodchain Brigade's Prism Powder.
So this is the Bloodchain Brigade again?
The question is... when?
Pathetic!
Now begone, Highlander!
Mimoza?!
So that's where the Prism Powder was?
My son was killed by a Highlander!
Go to hell!
Magicite beasts! Split up!
Wait!
You need to evacuate the people in the castle!
But...
Leave this to us! Hurry!
Understood.
What do we do, Chris?
We have to stop her.
Rani, if she looks like she's going to fire
another one of those beams, block her!
Got it!
Lady Seilyn, stop this, please!
No, Lady Seilyn!
You're...
Die!
Stop it!
Don't interfere!
I didn't come here to fight you!
You're with the Bloodchain
Brigade, aren't you?
And what if I am?
If I'd defeated you then, Mimoza wouldn't
have gotten her hands on the Prism Powder.
No, that's not true.
My comrades all carry Prism Powder.
Comrade Mimoza already had it.
When did he show up?
The plan to use the banished knights
to attack the Highlander failed.
So Comrade Mimoza took action on her own.
And who might you be?
I am the leader of the Bloodchain Brigade.
I have no name. Call me what you like.
I've come to protect this land.
From the danger that you people created?
We will eliminate the Highlander,
but the people of this land are innocent.
I won't let you hurt either of them.
Chris! We need to stop her!
Get out of here.
I won't let you!
I didn't think anyone could take a clean hit
from my Aether-Shell-enhanced fist.
It seems I still have much
to see of the world!
Step aside!
Sorry, but I can't.
Amazing!
I'd love to have a nice, long fight
with him, but now's not the time!
You're mine.
Not on my watch!
Then I'll take you out first!
Lady Seilyn!
Lady Seilyn, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
Are you in pain, Lady Seilyn?
No! Sistia!
Yes!
Lady Seilyn!
Run!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Lady Seilyn?
That's...
Lady Seilyn!
No!
Lady Seilyn, no!
Chris!
What are you doing?
You should've allowed her a clean death!
Lady Seilyn is still in there!
We can't let her die!
But nothing's changed.
There's something I want to try.
Distract her.
If I fail, I'll let you do as you like.
Very well. Let's make a deal.
Whether this works or not,
when it's over, you leave the city.
We're going to destroy
the Levitation Circle,
and I don't want you trying to interfere.
Very well.
I'm sorry I won't get a chance to fight you.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
We have a deal.
Sistia, distract her!
Understood!
You too, Rani!
Got it.
Chris, make sure you stop
Lady Seilyn, all right?
Yeah, I'll give it my best shot!
Firstly, I convert all of
my aether into mana.
I control it and shift into
casting a spell...
I'm ready to cast!
Freeze!
Oh?
Chris, are you okay?
Yeah, I think it worked.
Hey, Lady Seilyn's okay, right?
Yeah, magicite beasts are tough to kill.
I think she'll be able
to move when it melts.
Good...
But we need to get her away from here.
I'll make her easier to move, then.
She's too big right now.
She's getting smaller!
This light... Aether?
So he's a Divine Knight too?
But the Goddess' blessing
is needed to create a Divine Knight.
I thought I couldn't sense her
in this world...
Is there a divine existence here after all?
The aether in her body is gone,
so returning her to her original size
will be almost impossible.
But that also means that she can never again
grow large enough to be a threat to others.
I hate to say it, but I couldn't do
what you've done right now.
Keep your promise, then. Go.
What about the people
in the castle and the town?
We won't hurt them.
Our only enemy are the Highlanders.
I believe you.
Lady Seilyn!
Don't go!
She'll come back someday.
Really?
Yup. So all of you,
stay friends with each other!
So that when she comes back,
she'll be happy.
Okay...
Bye-bye, Lady Seilyn!
Come back, okay?
We'll be waiting!
Hey!
Lady Seilyn, stop moving
around like that! It tickles!
She's so cute after the ice melted!
Rani, please...
Well, mine are too small.
She seems to like your breasts better.
Right, Lyn?
Lyn?
She's so small now! So I thought "Lyn"
fit better than calling her "Lady Seilyn."
Lyn, come on outside...
Stop moving around!
What's wrong, Rani?
I still don't know who was right
and who was wrong this time.
The Bloodchain Brigade said they
were trying to protect the town.
Yup.
It just makes my head hurt!
That's just part of being young.
No, I don't think so...
It doesn't bother you, Chris?
Yup. 'Cause I don't think about it.
As long as you only think about
getting stronger, it won't bother you.
Want to try it, Rani?
I'll pass.
Then think about it all you like.
I'm always on your side, okay?
Yeah, thanks!
Do something!
Paradise
Comic by Kuromura Moto